A Guide to the Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
- General Counsel and Vice President Files, 1887-1942, 14.4 cubic feet (Box 1-32)
  - Legal Files, 1903-1942, 11.475 cubic feet (Box 3-27)
    - Johnson, Joseph E., case of, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Johnson, Laura, case of, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Johnson, Sam, case of, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Johnson, Thomas, case of, 1918-1919 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Johnson, W. I., case of, 1911-1913 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Johnston, Richard H., property sale and deed, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Jones and Lamb Company, case of, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Jones, Addie V., case of, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Jones, C. C., case of, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Jones, Catherine and G. W. Marshall and J. Russell Sykes, cases of, 1917-1918 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Jones, Eleanor, case of, 1918-1919 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Jones, George W., case of, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Jones, Lydia, case of, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Jones, Marie L., case of, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Jones, Grayson T., case of, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Jones, Norman T., testimony before the Securities and Exchange Commission (legal research files and exhibits), 1942 (Box 16a, Folder 1)
    - Jones, Norman T., testimony before the Securities and Exchange Commission (legal reserach files and exhibits), 1942 (Box 16a, Folder 2)
    - Jones, Norman T., testimony before the Securities and Exchange Commission (legal research files and exhibits), 1942 (Box 16a, Folder 3)
    - Jones, W. B., case of, 1915 (Box 16a, Folder 4)
    - Jones, W. S., case of, 1916 (Box 16a, Folder 5)
    - Joynes, N. B., property deeds, 1920 (Box 16a, Folder 6)
    - Cases: General - K, 1922-1925 (Box 16a, Folder 7)
    - Kaiama, Willie, case of, 1923 (Box 16a, Folder 8)
    - Kardian, Matilda, case of, 1920-1923 (Box 16a, Folder 9)
    - Karn, Lillie V., et. als., case of, 1915 (Box 16a, Folder 10)
    - Karn, Sarah E., case of, 1920 (Box 16a, Folder 11)
    - Kass and Lee Company, case of, 1911-1912 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Keller, Paul J., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Kelly, H. E., case of, 1918-1919 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Kelly, Molly, case of, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Kendricks, George C., case of, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Kendricks, George C., case of, 1922? (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Kendricks, George C., case of, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - King, J. W., case of, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - King, Rosa, case of, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - King, Waverly G., case of, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Kirby, T. E., case of, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Klamnowitz, Marshall, case of, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Knight, Amber E., case of, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Kucera, Josephine, case of (B1142), 1916 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Kucera, Josephine, case of (B1034), 1916 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Cases: General - L, 1922-1925 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Lachman, William, case of, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - LaFrance, Inc./ Gimbels, case of, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Lakeside line (Richmond) school tickets, 1912-1913 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Lambert, George W., case of, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Land, W. H., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Larchment Investment Corporation, gas mains right-of-way, 1914, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Laughrom, James A. (administrator of Laura Laughrom), case of, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Lavalle, Gus, case of, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Lawrence, J. S., case of, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Lawrence, J. S. (administrator of Robert M. Saunders), case of, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Lawson, Mary, case of, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Lawson, William, case of, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Lee, J. W., case of, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Lee, John W., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Lee, Shurman, case of, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Lee, Spencer and G. P. Crobarger, cases of, 1918, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Lee, W. F., case of, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Lerman, M., case of, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Lesner, William J., case of, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Lester, Rosa May, case of, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Lester Street Crossing (Richmond) bridge construction, January-August 1913 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Lester Street Crossing (Richmond) bridge construction, September-November 1913 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Lester Street Crossing (Richmond) bridge construction, December 1913 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Lester Street Crossing (Richmond) bridge construction, 1914-1916 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Lester Street Crossing (Richmond) bridge construction, 1917-1919 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Levee, L. J., case of, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Levitin, D., case of (B1002), 1916 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Levitin, D., case of (B2194), 1922 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Levy, Annie, case of, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Levy, Charles, case of, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Lewis-Hubbard-Slack Company, case of, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Lewis, Willie, case of, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - A, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - B, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - C, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - D, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - E-F, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - G, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - H-J, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - K-M, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - N-O, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - O, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - R, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - S, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - T-V, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - W, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, case of - Y, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Lexington Hotel fire, National Fire Protection Association quarterly, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Liberty Street (Norfolk) abandonment (B1519), 1919 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Liberty Street (Norfolk) abandonment and South Norfolk annexation (B1500), 1919 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Lightfoot, Ira D., case of, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Lipscomb, Carrie, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Lipshitz, Beatrice, case of, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Llewellyn, C. H., case of, 1917 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Locks, Nellie G., case of, 1915 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - London, S. J., case of, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Long, William M., case of, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Lopolo, Joe, case of, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Lowenberg, Harry L., case of, 1917 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Cases: General - M, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Cases: General - M, January-July 1924 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Cases: General - M, September 1924-March 1925 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - M. T. Elliott Motor Company, case of, 1917-1920 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Cases: General - Mc, 1924-1925 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - McCauley, Alice, case of, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - McCracken, John J., case of, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - McCraw, John T., case of, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - McFarland, M. V., case of, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - McGinn, Katherine E. (administrator of Charles McGinn), case of, 1920 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - McGovern, H. S., case of, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - McGowan, R. L., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - McGuire, Lucille, case of, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - McGuire, Lucille, case of (testimony of McGuire), 30 May 1916 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - McKennon, Phillip, case of, 1915-1916 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - McLean, Nannie Isabel, case of, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - McLemore, James L., case of (B1156), 1916 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - McLemore, James L., case of (B1121), 1916-1917 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - McPherson, Margaret I., case of, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - McVeigh, L. W., case of, 1915-1916 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Malizzio, Jimmie, case of, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Mallory, G. W., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Mansbach, Louis, case of, 1919 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Marchant, J. F., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Marine Supply Company, case of, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Marshall, K. M., case of, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Martens, W. M., case of, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Martin, R. L. W., case of, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Martin, W. H., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Maryland Dredging and Contracting Company, case of, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Mason, John A. L., case of, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Masons and Boush Creek (Norfolk) bridge repairs, case of, 1919-1920 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Masons and Boush Creek (Norfolk) bridge repairs, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Masons and Boush Creek (Norfolk) bridge repairs, case of, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Matthews, F. D., case of, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Mayo, Charles, case of, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Mayo, George W., case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Mayo, Walter E., case of, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Meadows, J. G., case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Mendelson, Jennie, case of, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Mervis, M. I., case of, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Metzger, Benjamin F., property deed (Norfolk), 1919 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Mickens, Henry, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Midgette, Oliver C., case of, 1917-1918 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Military conscription and service, response to, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Miller and Rhoads, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Millhouse, Roy, case of, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Milton, Pearl, case of, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Minor, Herbert, case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous legal files, 1916-1936 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous pending cases, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous pending cases, 1922-1925 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Mizell, Dora, case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Moore, Alfred, case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Moore, Bernard C., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Moore, C. C., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Moore, Sarah, case of, 1915-1916 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Morien, Annie M., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Morgan, J. W., case of, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Morris, Abram (administrator of Sarah Morris), case of, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Morris and Nelson, case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Morris, W. S. (administrator of Percy W. Puffer), case of, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Moseley, Calvin, case of, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Moseley, Lillye R., case of, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Mosen, Neta, case of, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Moss, Martha, case of, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Moton, Sidney, case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Motor Sales and Service Company, case of, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Motormen and conductors' uniform changes, 1913-1914 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Motor Transit Corporation, cases and legal matters concerning, July 1914 and 1 April 1915 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Motor Transit Corporation, cases and legal matters concerning, 2 April-May 1915 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Motor Transit Corporation, cases and legal matters concerning, June 1915 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Motor Transit Corporation, cases and legal matters concerning, July-October 1915 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Motor Transit Corporation, cases and legal matters concerning, November-December 1915 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Motor Transit Corporation, cases and legal matters concerning, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Munden, Earser, case of, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Murdaugh, Charlie, case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Murdaugh, Mollie, case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Murden, Alice J., case of, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Murden, H. H., case of, 1916-1921 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Murden, Zack, case of, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Murray, Quarles (administrator for Percy Murray), case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Murray, R. W., case of, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Myers, Frank C., case of, 1915 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Myers, Joseph P., case of, 1919-1920 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Cases: General - N, 1923-1924 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - N. H. Slack Grocery, case of, 1918-1919 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Nagle, Sam, case of, 1916 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - National Plating Works, case of, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - National Surety Company (P. R. Metcalfe account), case of, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Nebett, Thomas C., case of, 1915 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Nelson, H. K., case of, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Nelson, Lizzie, case of, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Newberg, Sol, case of, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Newton, G. F., case of, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Newton, W. L., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Nicholson, Sarah, case of, 1919 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Nicholson, T. A., case of, 1917 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Nickerson, John, Jr., public utility circulars, 1916-1917 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Nimmo, Annie, case of, 1923 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View Railway Company (also Norfolk City and Suburban Railway and Indian River Park and Improvement Company), contracts with, December 1911-May 1912 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View Railway Company (also Norfolk City and Suburban Railway and Indian River Park and Improvement Company), contracts with, July-October 1912 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk and Ocean View Railway Company (also Norfolk City and Suburban Railway and Indian River Park and Improvement Company), contracts with, November 1912-April 1913 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Norfolk and Western Railway Company, agreement to construct tracks to City Gas Company of Norfolk, 1907-March 1917 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Norfolk and Western Railway Company, agreement to construct tracks to City Gas Company of Norfolk, April 1917-1919 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Norfolk and Western Railway demurrage claim, case of, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Norfolk Bay Shore Terminal, case of, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Norfolk Cab and Carriage Company, case of, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Norfolk Chamber of Commerce, reorganization of, 1913-1917 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Norfolk Commission for the Purchase and Improvement of Roads, case of, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Norfolk motormen and conductors' strike, 1917-1919 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Norfolk paving and franchise rights, cases of, May-June 1914 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Norfolk paving and franchise rights, cases of, July-October 1914 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Norfolk paving and franchise rights, cases of, November 1914 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Norfolk paving and franchise rights, cases of, December 1914-January 1915 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Norfolk paving and franchise rights, cases of, February 1915-September 1915 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Norfolk paving and franchise rights, cases of (related research documents and briefs), n. d. (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Norfolk paving and franchise rights, cases of (related research documents and briefs), n. d. (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Norfolk railway line, construction agreements, February 1918 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Norfolk railway line, construction agreements, 1-14 March 1918 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Norfolk railway line, construction agreements, 15-31 March 1918 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Norfolk railway line, construction agreements, April-September 1918 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Norfolk railway line, construction agreements, October-November 1918 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Corporation, complaint of, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Norfolk Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Corporation, property deed, 1920 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Norman, S. N., case of, 1916 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Norwood, L. A., case of, 1920-1921 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Nottingham and Wrenn Company, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Novo, Joe, case of, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Nunnally, Mabel G. (administrator for Alozo W. Nunnally), case of, 1917 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Cases: General - O, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Oakes, Adriana, case of, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Oakwood and Main line (Richmond), case of, 1917-1920 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Oakwood and Main line (Richmond), case of (related research documents and briefs), n. d. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Ocheltree, J. L., case of, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - O'Connor, L. C., case of, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - O'Flaherty, D. C., case of, 1911-1916 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - O'Flaherty, D. C., case of (briefs), 1914 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Ogburn, Robert, case of, 1920 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Old Dominion Iron and Nail Works Company, land titles, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Old Dominion Tire Company, case of, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Oliver, G. W., case of, 1918 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Oliver, Lucy R., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - , case of, 19 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Ostranger, J. E., case of, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Oursler, Ira A., case of, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Owens, Harriett, case of, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Cases: General - P, December 1923-April 1924 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Cases: General - P, May 1924-March 1925 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Parham, James, case of, 1923 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Parker, C. R., case of, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Parrish, C. L., case of, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Parrish, Octavia R., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Parsley, Luther J. (administrator for Luther W. Parsley), case of, 1922-1923 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Patterson, R. A., right-of-way dispute, case of, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Patterson, R. A., right-of-way dispute, case of, 1914-1915 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Patterson, R. A., right-of-way dispute, case of (briefs), 1908 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Patterson, R. A., right-of-way dispute, case of (briefs), 1908 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Pavey, Darwin K., case of, 1920 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - "Pay-As-You-Enter" patent, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Payne, Dalton, case of, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Perkinson, K. B., case of, 1915-1916 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Perry, Mollie, case of, 1918-1919 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Person, Adam, case of, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Petersburg-Hopewell and City Point Railway Company, case of, 1920-1921 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Petersburg railroad track extension, bids for, 1912 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Petersburg water supply, contract with, 1913 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Pettus, J. H., case of, 1915-1916 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Phaup, J. C., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Phelps, Lillian E. (administrator for P. L. Phelps), case of, 1916 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Phields, Rosa Lee, case of, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Phillips, Cora O., case of, 1919-1920 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Pierce, Ruth C. (administrator for Henry L. Pierce), case of, 1917-1919 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Pipkin, Dan, case of, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Pitt, Oscar Lee, case of, 1921 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Pitts, Lelia Taylor, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Polen, Jennie (administrator for H. Polen), case of, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Portlock, Sarah E., case of, 1922 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Portsmouth, single track loop construction and right-of-way ordinance, 1919 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Portsmouth Baseball Club, subscription request, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Portsmouth, Berkeley, and Suffolk Water Company, contract of, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Portsmouth Company, property transaction, 1916-1919 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Portsmouth Line, agreements and contracts with Seaboard Airline, 1912-1915 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Portsmouth Line, agreements and contracts with Seaboard Airline, 1916-1919 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Portsmouth Suffolk Bus Corporation, case of, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Postal Telegraph Company, contract with, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Powell, Rosetta, case of, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Power lines territory tributary, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Powhatan Vaneer and Basket Company, case of, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Pratt, Jake, case of, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Preston, Hunter, case of, 1915, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Prettyman, C. F., case of (B1159), 1917 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Prettyman, C. F., case of (B1179), 1917 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Price, A. D., case of, 1915, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Price, Beryl, case of, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Priddy contract, case of, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Prieur, William Lee, case of, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Prince George Electric Light and Power Company, agreement with, 1918 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Prince George Electric Light and Power Company, agreement with, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Public liability insurance, 1921 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Puller, J. J., case of, 1919-1920 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Purity Ice Cream Company, case of, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Cases: General - Q, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Quartermus, James Benjamin (administrator of Katherine Quartermus), case of, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Quartermus, James T. (administrator of James T. Quartermus, Jr.), case of, 1919 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Quillin, E. S. (administrator of Isaac S. Quillin), case of, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Cases: General - R, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Cases: General - R, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Cases: General - R, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Railroad crossing safety, 1914-1915 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Railways and Light Company of America, equipment contract, 1912-1915 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Raines, Rosena, case of, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Rall, Bertha, case of, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Rathberger, Leota Rathbun, case of, 1918, 1924 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Rawl, S. H., case of, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Raymond, Margaret, case of, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Ready, George E., case of, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Redford, E. W., case of, 1923 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Reeves Avenue Power Station, contract of, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Reilly, M. J., case of, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Rexoler, Helen, case of, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Rhodes, J. W., case of, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Rice, C. H., case of, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, charter extracts and Chesterfield County franchise, 1912 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, construction contract with Cleveland Construction Company (copy), 1901 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, General Assembly act of incorporation with amendments (copy), 1898-1901 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, petitions to Chesterfield County Board of Supervisors, 1901 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, 1908-January 1912 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, February-[?] March 1912 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, [?] March 1912 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Richmond and Rappahannock Railway Company, agreement with, [?] March-30 March 1912 (Box 22, Folder 52)